

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211





Divesh Agrawal Divesh Agrawal Reatured 7 BI Developer seeking roles in MicroStrategy Admin/Developer, Business Intelligence, Data Modeling, Business Analytics, Data Visualization, Project Administration, Project Management, Project Monitoring, JIRA, Service Now, Tableau Current Designation: Senior Microstrategy Developer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 4 Month(s) Current Company: Infocepts Technologies Notice Period: 3 Months Current Location: Nagpur Highest Degree: MTech [Computers] Pref. Location: Hyderabad, Pune, Nagpur Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Maintenance Role: Business Analyst Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Single/unmarried $\label{thm:contracted} \textit{Key Skills: BI Developer,} McroStrategy, \textit{Business Intelligence,} \textit{Data Modeling,} \textit{Business Analytics,} \textit{Data Modeling,} \textit{Data Modeling,$ Visualization, Project Administration, Project Management, Project Monitoring, JIRA, Service Now, Tableau, Business Analyst, Senior Microstrategy Developer Verified : L Phone Number | Email - id

Jump to Section Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Last Active: 22-Jan-21

5 Years of delivering analytical and problem solving skills and ability to follow through with projects from inception to

Proven ability to successfully work for multiple requirements, design, and development approaches and methodologies (agile, Waterfall, etc.)

Experience in Mcro-strategy 11.x 2019/20 and 10.x development tasks like creation of schema objects, application objects, configuration objects, dossiers and involved in creation of LDM, PDM architecture for project. Also involved in administration tasks like installing, configuring database instance, project administration, job monitoring, security roles, folder level security, user management, user ACLs, running and creating command manager outlines, object migration, project duplication, etc. Certified in MicroStrategy 10.112 Analytics Reporting Knowledge, 10.141 Documents Knowledge, 10.311 Administration for Enterprise Analytics Knowledge.

Work Experience

Infocepts Technologies as Senior Microstrategy Developer Feb 2018 to Till Date

It is a media and entertainment company engaged in the production and marketing of entertainment, news and information products with services to a global customer base. The company owns and operates American television networks, numerous cable channels and a group of local stations in US. In 2017 with \$33 Billion it is one of the largest media and entertainment company in US.

Responsibilities

Involved in creation of LDM for project.

Created and configure database instance and catalog data warehouse.

Creation of schema objects, application objects and configuration objects.

Worked for ad hoc reporting project which contains only objects as per client requirement.

Worked for canned report as per client requirement.

Worked on admin tasks like migration Dev to QA and QA to Prod, Integrity Manager.

Created standard reports, OLAP reports, Documents and intelligent cubes.

Worked on JIRA and Service now tickets.

Created various types of filters.

Created Rich and interactive reports, documents and Dossiers with various formatting options.

Excellon Software as Functional Consultant

Apr 2016 to Jan 2018

Requirement gathering, preparation of functional specifications, configuration documentation, creation of testing plan, cutover, technical go-live, production go-live and doing first level production support.

Done all standard and custom configurations.?

Trained more than 100+ people for Bajaj users and handled all the situations at the time of rollouts.

Trained team of 20+ people for configuration and getting extensive testing done from them.

Prepared all documents like Workshop Material, Training Documents, Configuration documents, FAQ documents,

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

runcional specification, DRD, FRD, etc.
Onsite exposure to support Business within India.
Handled change requests.
Taking knowledge transfer sessions, Guiding and mentoring new project members.
Analyzing various support issues & providing solutions for them.?
Created cutover plan and performed cutover activities, supported project during go live.

• HCL Infosystems Limited as Apprentice Engineer Sep 2013 to May 2014

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from J L Chaturvedi College Of Engg in 2013

PG: M.Tech (Computers) from GH raisoni college of Engineering, Nagpur in 2016

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Tableau

11.011 & 10.011 MCSA, 11.012 & 10.012 MCMA, 11.019 & 10.019 MCSAD, 11.020 & 10.020 MCMAD,

11.xMcroStrategy Certified Specialist Analyst, 11.xMcroStrategy Certified Specialist Admin

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Microstrategy 11.x, 10.4, 10.10 TABLEAU 10.3 Normalized, De-Normalized Moderately De-Normalized MS-SQL Server 2012, MS Access Informatica 9.1 JIRA, Service Now			
TABLEAU 10.3 Normalized, De-Normalized Moderately De-Normalized MS-SQL Server 2012, MS Access Informatica 9.1 JIRA, Service Now	Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
Normalized, De-Normalized Moderately De-Normalized MS-SQL Server 2012, MS Access Informatica 9.1 JIRA, Service Now	Microstrategy 11.x, 10.4, 10.10		
Moderately De-Normalized MS-SQL Server 2012, MS Access Informatica 9.1 JIRA, Service Now	TABLEAU 10.3		
MS-SQL Server 2012, MS Access Informatica 9.1 JIRA, Service Now	Normalized, De-Normalized		
Informatica 9.1 JIRA, Service Now	Moderately De-Normalized		
JIRA, Service Now	MS-SQL Server 2012, MS Access		
	Informatica 9.1		
	JIRA, Service Now		
WINDOWS	WINDOWS		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
ENGLISH				
HINDI				

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Media Domain Project Client: Digital Domain Nature of Employment: Full Time Role: Other

Duration: Jul 2018 - Jul 2020 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 2

Skill Used: MicroStrategy

Role Description: I worked as a Senior Analyst. Development and admin tasks comes under me. I am responsible for creating the reports, documents as per client requirements.

Project Details: In this project I worked as a key member of the project. I developed this project from scratch, I had created the LDM, Schema objects, Application objects, DBI, DSN, Subscription, etc. I also worked on admin tasks like on Object Manager, System Manager, Command Manager, Integrity Manager, License Manager. End to end project development and support all things I have handled in this project.

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent
Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.